<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="18"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[The Holy Rosary for
                        The Holy Rosary for






                                          Vocations
                                           Vocations]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[The Holy Rosary is an ancient form of prayer in the Church that dates back to

               the early Middle Ages.  Through this meditative prayer, we join our prayers with
               those  of  the  Blessed  Virgin  Mary  in  asking  God  for  what  we  need.           It  is  a

               powerful prayer, indeed.

               This guide is meant to assist those who pray to focus their prayer of the Rosary

               for the intentions of Vocations in the Archdiocese of Baltimore.  As you pray and
               meditate on the mysteries, please remember to pray for those who hear God’s

               call to service in the Church as priests, deacons, bishops, consecrated men and
               women and holy husbands and wives.  Pray that you know your vocation and

               follow it with generosity and joy.

               And finally, know that in making this prayer your own you are united not only

               with Mary and the angels and the saints, but with fellow believers everywhere.


               Pray the Master of the Harvest to send laborers into His vineyard!








               How to Pray the Rosary



               On the crucifix, pray the Apostles’ Creed:

                       I believe in God, the Father Almighty, Creator of Heaven and earth;

                                      and in Jesus Christ, His only Son Our Lord,
                 Who was conceived by the Holy Spirit, born of the Virgin Mary, suffered under

                                 Pontius Pilate, was crucified, died, and was buried.
                       He descended into Hell; the third day He rose again from the dead;

                He ascended into Heaven, and sits at the right hand of God, the Father almighty;
                            from thence He shall come to judge the living and the dead.
                  I believe in the Holy Spirit, the holy Catholic Church, the communion of saints,

                    the forgiveness of sins, the resurrection of the body and life everlasting.
                                                          Amen.]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[On the next single bead, an Our Father.

                                            Our Father, who art in heaven,

                                                 hallowed be thy name.
                                         Thy kingdom come, thy will be done
                                               on earth as it is in heaven.
                                            Give us this day our daily bread,
                   and forgive us our trespasses, as we forgive those who trespass against us.
                                           And lead us not into temptation,
                                                but deliver us from evil.
                                                          Amen.


               On the next three, pray a Hail Mary each, for an increase in the virtues of Faith,
               Hope and Love.


                                                Hail, Mary, full of grace!
                                                  The Lord is with thee.
                                            Blessed art thou among women
                                     and blessed is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus.

                                              Holy Mary, Mother of God,
                                                   pray for us sinners,
                                          now and at the hour of our death.
                                                           Amen

               On the next single, a Glory Be.


                           Glory be to the Father and to the Son and to the Holy Spirit,
                     as it was in the beginning, is now, and ever shall be, world without end.
                                                           Amen


               Each decade begins with a meditation on the mystery, then an Our Father, 10 Hail
               Mary’s and one Glory Be, completed with the Fatima Prayer:


                           O my Jesus, forgive us our sins; save us from the fires of hell;
                       lead all souls to heaven, especially those most in need of Thy mercy.


                After all five decades, pray the Hail, Holy Queen, then “Pray for us, O Holy Mother
                      of God,” then the Rosary prayer, “O God, Whose only-begotten Son…”:]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[Hail Holy Queen,

                                                    mother of mercy,
                                        our life, our sweetness and our hope.
                                 To thee do we cry, poor, banished children of Eve;
                                           to thee do we send up our sighs,
                                     mourning and weeping in this vale of tears.
                       Turn then, most gracious advocate, thine eyes of mercy towards us,
                  And after this our exile show unto us the blessed fruit of your womb, Jesus.
                                      O clement, o loving, o sweet Virgin Mary!


                                          Pray for us, O holy Mother of God,
                              that we may be made worthy of the promises of Christ.

               Let us pray:


                                                          O God,
                                               whose only-begotten Son,
                                          by his life, death and resurrection,

                                  has purchased for us the rewards of eternal life,
                                                grant, we beseech Thee,
                     that while meditating on these holy mysteries of the Most Holy Rosary
                                               of the Blessed Virgin Mary,
                        we may imitate what they contain and obtain what they promise,
                                      through  this same Christ our Lord.  Amen.]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[J Jo oy yf fu ul l   M My ys st te er ri ie es s


               The Annunciation

                                                              In the sixth month, the angel Gabriel was sent

                                                              from God to a town of Galilee called Nazareth,
                                                              to a virgin betrothed to a man named Joseph,
                                                              of  the  house  of  David,  and  the  virgin’s  name
                                                              was  Mary.  And  coming  to  her,  he  said,  “Hail,
                                                              favored one! The Lord is with you.” But she was
                                                              greatly troubled at what was said and pondered
                                                              what  sort  of  greeting  this  might  be.  Then  the
                                                              angel said to her, “Do not be afraid, Mary, for
                                                              you  have  found  favor  with  God.   Behold,  you
                                                              will conceive in your womb and bear a son, and

                                                              you shall name him Jesus.  He will be great and
                                                              will  be  called  Son  of  the  Most  High,  and  the
                                                              Lord God will give him the throne of David his
               father, and he will rule over the house of Jacob forever, and of his kingdom there will be no
               end.” But Mary said to the angel, “How can this be, since I have no relations with a man?” And
               the angel said to her in reply, “The holy Spirit will come upon you, and the power of the Most
               High will overshadow you. Therefore the child to be born will be called holy, the Son of God.
               And behold, Elizabeth, your relative, has also conceived a son in her old age, and this is the sixth
               month  for  her  who  was  called  barren;  for  nothing  will  be  impossible  for  God.”  Mary  said,

               “Behold, I am the handmaid of the Lord. May it be done to me according to your word.” Then
               the angel departed from her. (Luke 1:26-38)

               God,
               your Word comes to us as a gentle invitation
               to know you better and to follow your will.
               Help us to be open to your call in our lives,
               and, like Mary, to respond to that call generously.
               Guide those whom you have called to priesthood and consecrated life
               to dedicate themselves to you as your servants.
               We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.

               Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[The Visitation


               During  those  days  Mary  set  out  and
               traveled to the hill country in haste to a
               town of Judah, where she entered the
               house  of  Zechariah  and  greeted

               Elizabeth.   When     Elizabeth  heard
               Mary’s  greeting,  the  infant  leaped  in
               her  womb,  and  Elizabeth,  filled  with
               the holy Spirit, cried out in a loud voice
               and said, “Most blessed are you among
               women, and blessed is the fruit of your
               womb.  And  how  does  this  happen  to
               me, that the mother of my Lord should come to me?  For at the moment the sound of your
               greeting  reached  my  ears,  the  infant  in  my  womb  leaped  for  joy.  Blessed  are  you  who
               believed that what was spoken to you by the Lord would be fulfilled.” (Luke 1:39-45)


               God,
               your life stirs our hearts to love and to service.
               Help us to seek you ever more in service to our brothers and sisters,
               and lead those who hear your call to priesthood and consecrated life
               to give you glory through lives of faithful service.
               We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.

               Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…

                                                            The Birth of the Lord


                                                            In  those  days  a  decree  went  out  from  Caesar
                                                            Augustus that  the  whole  world  should  be
                                                            enrolled.  This  was  the  first  enrollment,  when
                                                            Quirinius was governor of Syria. So all went to be
                                                            enrolled, each to his own town. And Joseph too
                                                            went up from Galilee from the town of Nazareth

                                                            to  Judea,  to  the  city  of  David  that  is  called
                                                            Bethlehem,  because  he  was  of  the  house  and
                                                            family  of  David,  to  be  enrolled  with  Mary,  his
                                                            betrothed, who was with child. While they were
                                                            there,  the  time  came  for  her  to  have  her  child,
                                                            and  she  gave  birth  to  her  firstborn  son. She
                                                            wrapped him in swaddling clothes and laid him in]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[a manger, because there was no room for them in the inn. (Luke 2:1-7)


               God,
               your Son became flesh for the salvation of the world.
               Hear us as we ask you
               to raise up in your Church new servants of your incarnate Word,
               to make Jesus present through the sacraments
               and through loving service to others.
               We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.

               Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…

               The Presentation of the Lord


               When the days were completed for their
               purification according  to  the  law  of
               Moses, they took him up to Jerusalem to
               present  him  to  the  Lord,  just  as  it  is
               written  in  the  law  of  the  Lord,  “Every
               male  that  opens  the  womb  shall  be
               consecrated to the Lord,” and to offer the
               sacrifice of “a pair of turtledoves or two
               young  pigeons,”  in  accordance  with  the

               dictate in the law of the Lord.

               Now there was a man in Jerusalem whose
               name  was  Simeon.  This  man  was
               righteous and devout, awaiting the consolation of Israel, and the holy Spirit was upon him. It
               had been revealed to him by the holy Spirit that he should not see death before he had seen
               the  Messiah  of  the  Lord.  He  came  in  the  Spirit  into  the  temple;  and  when  the  parents
               brought in the child Jesus to perform the custom of the law in regard to him, he took him
               into his arms and blessed God, saying: “Now, Master, you may let your servant go in peace,

               according to your word, for my eyes have seen your salvation, which you prepared in sight of
               all the peoples, a light for revelation to the Gentiles, and glory for your people Israel.” The
               child’s father and mother were amazed at what was said about him; and Simeon blessed
               them and said to Mary his mother, “Behold, this child is destined for the fall and rise of
               many  in  Israel,  and to be  a  sign  that  will  be  contradicted  (and  you  yourself  a  sword  will
               pierce) so that the thoughts of many hearts may be revealed.” (Luke 2:22-35)


               God,
               as your Son was presented in the Temple]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[as your gift to Mary and Joseph,
               help us to offer to you our lives in response to your call.
               May those who hear a call to priesthood and consecrated life
               generously offer their gifts of themselves
               and find the courage to be signs of contradiction in our world.
               We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.

               Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…

               The Finding of Christ in the Temple


               Each year his parents went to Jerusalem for the feast of Passover, and when he was twelve
               years old, they went up according to festival custom. After they had completed its days, as they
                                                            were returning, the boy Jesus remained behind in
                                                            Jerusalem,  but  his  parents  did  not  know  it.
                                                            Thinking  that  he  was  in  the  caravan,  they
                                                            journeyed  for  a  day  and  looked  for  him  among
                                                            their relatives and acquaintances, but not finding
                                                            him, they returned to Jerusalem to look for him.
                                                            After  three  days  they  found  him  in  the  temple,

                                                            sitting  in  the  midst  of  the  teachers,  listening  to
                                                            them  and  asking  them  questions,  and  all  who
                                                            heard  him  were  astounded  at  his  understanding
                                                            and his answers. When his parents saw him, they
                                                            were  astonished,  and  his  mother  said  to  him,
                                                            “Son, why have you done this to us? Your father
               and  I  have  been  looking  for  you  with  great  anxiety.”  And  he  said  to  them,  “Why  were  you
               looking  for  me?  Did  you  not  know  that  I  must  be  in  my  Father’s  house?”  But  they  did  not

               understand what he said to them. He went down with them and came to Nazareth, and was
               obedient to them; and his mother kept all these things in her heart. And Jesus advanced [in]
               wisdom and age and favor before God and man.  (Luke 2:41-52)

               God,
               help us to seek you where you may be found.
               May we who hear your call to be your light to the world
               find the courage to offer to you lives of service and joy
               in response to the generous gifts of life and love you have given to us.
               We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.

               Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[L Lu um mi in no ou us s   M My ys st te er ri ie es s


               The Baptism of the Lord

               It  happened  in  those  days  that  Jesus  came  from

               Nazareth of Galilee and was baptized in the Jordan by
               John.  On  coming  up  out  of  the  water  he  saw  the
               heavens  being  torn  open  and  the  Spirit,  like  a  dove,
               descending  upon  him.   And  a  voice  came  from  the
               heavens, “You are my beloved Son; with you I am well
               pleased.” (Mark 1:9-11)




               Lord God,
               in our Baptism you have given each of us a unique vocation.
               Help us to live lives of holiness and dedication to you.
               May we always seek to do your will
               and be found worthy to hear that you are well pleased with us.
               We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.

               Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…

               The Wedding at Cana

                                                                  On  the  third  day  there  was  a  wedding in
                                                                  Cana in  Galilee,  and  the  mother  of  Jesus

                                                                  was there. Jesus and his disciples were also
                                                                  invited to the wedding. When the wine ran
                                                                  short,  the  mother  of  Jesus  said  to  him,
                                                                  “They  have  no  wine.”   [And]  Jesus  said  to
                                                                  her,  “Woman,  how  does  your  concern
                                                                  affect me? My hour has not yet come.” His
                                                                  mother  said  to  the  servers,  “Do  whatever
                                                                  he  tells  you.” Now  there  were  six  stone
                                                                  water  jars  there  for  Jewish  ceremonial
                                                                  washings,  each  holding  twenty  to  thirty
               gallons. Jesus told them, “Fill the jars with water.” So they filled them to the brim. Then he told

               them,  “Draw  some  out  now  and  take  it  to  the  headwaiter.” So  they  took  it.  And  when  the
               headwaiter  tasted  the  water  that  had  become  wine,  without  knowing  where  it  came  from
               (although the servers who had drawn the water knew), the headwaiter called the bridegroom]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[and said to him, “Everyone serves good wine first, and then when people have drunk freely, an
               inferior one; but you have kept the good wine until now.” Jesus did this as the beginning of his

               signs in Cana in Galilee and so revealed his glory, and his disciples began to believe in him. (John
               2:1-11)

               Lord God,
               at Cana Jesus blessed marriage as a reflection of His love for the Church.
               May those who are called to this vocation of love
                       be found chaste and faithful in their vows,
               and may those who are called to be your brides and bridegrooms
                       in vocations of service remain single-hearted
                       in their dedication to you and your Church.
               We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.

               Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…

               The Preaching of the Kingdom


               After  John  had  been  arrested, Jesus  came  to  Galilee
               proclaiming  the  gospel  of  God: “This  is  the  time  of
               fulfillment. The kingdom of God is at hand. Repent, and
               believe in the gospel.” (Mark 1:14-15)

               Lord God,
               your Word reaches to the ends of the earth.
               Send more ministers of that Word into the world
               to share the richness of your life with a world that so
               desperately needs it.
               We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.

               Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…

                                                       The Transfiguration of the Lord


                                                       After six days Jesus took Peter, James, and John and
                                                       led them up a high mountain apart by themselves. And
                                                       he  was  transfigured  before  them,  and  his  clothes
                                                       became  dazzling  white,  such  as  no  fuller  on  earth
                                                       could  bleach  them.  Then  Elijah  appeared  to  them
                                                       along  with  Moses,  and  they  were  conversing  with
                                                       Jesus.  Then Peter said to Jesus in reply, “Rabbi, it is
                                                       good that we are here! Let us make three tents: one]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[for you, one for Moses, and one for Elijah.” He hardly knew what to say, they were so terrified.
               Then a cloud came, casting a shadow over them; then from the cloud came a voice, “This is my

               beloved Son. Listen to him.” Suddenly, looking around, they no longer saw anyone but Jesus
               alone with them. (Mark 9:2-8)

               Lord God,
               in Jesus we see the fullness of your revelation to the world.
               Help us to remain fixed on His light,
               and help those whom you call to the priesthood and consecrated life
                       to reflect that light to the world.
               We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.

               Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…

               The Institution of the Eucharist

                                                                                  While they were eating, he
                                                                                  took    bread,   said   the
                                                                                  blessing, broke it, and gave

                                                                                  it to them, and said, “Take
                                                                                  it;  this  is  my  body.”  Then
                                                                                  he took a cup, gave thanks,
                                                                                  and  gave  it  to  them,  and
                                                                                  they  all  drank  from  it.  He
                                                                                  said  to  them,  “This  is  my
                                                                                  blood  of  the  covenant,
                                                                                  which  will  be  shed for
                                                                                  many. Amen, I say to you, I
               shall not drink again the fruit of the vine until the day when I drink it new in the kingdom of
               God.” (Mark 14:22-25)


               Lord God,
               in the Eucharist we receive the fullness of your life and love;
               we taste heaven and are promised eternal life.
               Send more faithful servants of this mystery into your Church
               and raise up new priests to renew this Sacrament of love.
               We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[S So or rr ro ow wf fu ul l   M My ys st te er ri ie es s


               The Agony in the Garden

               Then they came to a place named Gethsemane, and he said to

               his  disciples,  “Sit  here  while  I  pray.”  He  took  with  him  Peter,
               James, and John, and began to be troubled and distressed. Then
               he said to them, “My soul is sorrowful even to death. Remain
               here  and  keep  watch.”  He  advanced  a  little  and  fell  to  the
               ground and prayed that if it were possible the hour might pass
               by  him;  he  said,  “Abba,  Father, all  things  are  possible  to  you.
               Take this cup away from me, but not what I will but what you
               will.” (Mark 14:32-36)


               Lord,
               often we feel burdened beyond our ability to endure.
               Help us to see in your holy will the freedom of the children of God.
               Give to those who hear a call to priesthood and consecrated life
               the strength and courage to respond to your will generously and with love.
               We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.

               Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…

               The Scourging at the Pillar


                                           Pilate then summoned the chief priests, the rulers, and the people
                                           and said to them, “You brought this man to me and accused him of
                                           inciting the people to revolt. I have conducted my investigation in
                                           your presence and have not found this man guilty of the charges
                                           you have brought against him, nor did Herod, for he sent him back
                                           to us. So no capital crime has been committed by him. Therefore I
                                           shall have him flogged and then release him.”  (Luke 23:13-16)


                                           Lord,
                                           this world does not always understand
                                                   the choice to sacrifice all for the sake of heaven.
                                           Assist  those  who  are  following  a  call  to  priesthood  and
                                           consecrated life
                                           to endure the hardships that their generous gift of self
                                                   can bring upon them.
                                           We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.
               Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…]]></page><page Index="13"><![CDATA[The Crowning with Thorns


               The soldiers wove a crown out of thorns and placed it on
               his  head,  and  clothed  him  in  a  purple  cloak,  and  they
               came to him and said, “Hail, King of the Jews!” And they
               struck  him  repeatedly.  Once  more  Pilate  went  out  and

               said to them, “Look, I am bringing him out to you, so that
               you may know that I find no guilt in him.” So Jesus came
               out, wearing the crown of thorns and the purple cloak.
               And he said to them, “Behold, the man!” (John 19:2-5)

               Lord,
               Jesus is the King of kings and Lord of lords.
               May those who hear your call to serve the King
                       in lives of priesthood or consecrated life
               joyfully show forth the Kingdom of Heaven
                       to all to whom they are sent.
               We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.

               Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…

               Jesus Carries His Cross

                                                 So  they  took  Jesus,  and  carrying  the  cross  himself he  went
                                                 out  to  what  is  called  the  Place  of  the  Skull,  in  Hebrew,
                                                 Golgotha. (John 19:16-17)


                                                 Lord,
                                                 Jesus calls us to pick up our crosses and follow Him.
                                                 May those who follow Him in lives dedicated to the Church
                                                 find the strength to continue in their fidelity
                                                 and joyfully bear their crosses for His sake.
                                                 We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.

                                                 Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…]]></page><page Index="14"><![CDATA[The Crucifixion


               They  brought  him  to  the  place  of  Golgotha  (which  is
               translated Place of the Skull). They gave him wine drugged
               with myrrh, but he did not take it. Then they crucified him
               and  divided  his  garments  by  casting  lots  for  them  to  see

               what  each  should  take.  It  was  nine  o’clock  in  the
               morning when  they  crucified  him. The  inscription  of  the
               charge against him read, “The King of the Jews.” With him
               they crucified two revolutionaries, one on his right and one
               on his left. (Mark 15:22-27)

               Lord,
               on the Cross Jesus offered you the perfect sacrifice:
               all that he had and all that he is.
               Inspire more young people to respond
                       to your call to service in the Church
               with lives of total dedication to your People.
               We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.

               Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…]]></page><page Index="15"><![CDATA[G Gl lo or ri io ou us s   M My ys st te er ri ie es s


               The Resurrection of the Lord

                                                     After  the  sabbath,  as  the  first  day  of  the  week  was

                                                     dawning, Mary Magdalene and the other Mary came to
                                                     see the tomb. And behold, there was a great earthquake;
                                                     for  an  angel  of  the  Lord  descended  from  heaven,
                                                     approached,  rolled back  the  stone,  and  sat upon  it. His
                                                     appearance was like lightning and his clothing was white
                                                     as snow. The guards were shaken with fear of him and
                                                     became  like  dead  men.  Then  the  angel  said  to  the
                                                     women in reply, “Do not be afraid! I know that you are
                                                     seeking  Jesus  the  crucified. He  is  not  here,  for  he  has
                                                     been  raised  just  as  he  said.  Come  and  see  the  place

                                                     where he lay. Then go quickly and tell his disciples, ‘He
                                                     has  been  raised from the  dead,  and  he  is  going  before
                                                     you to Galilee; there you will see him.’ Behold, I have told
               you.” (Matthew 28:1-7)

               Heavenly Father,
               the resurrection of Jesus brought the hope of new life to the world.
               Help those who are called to make disciples of the nations
               to draw their strength and hope
                       from the assurance that He lives and reigns forever.
               We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.

               Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…

               The Ascension of the Lord

               When  they  had  gathered  together  they  asked
               him, “Lord, are you at this time going to restore

               the kingdom to Israel?” He answered them, “It
               is not for you to know the times or seasons that
               the  Father  has  established  by  his  own
               authority. But you will receive power when the
               holy Spirit comes upon you, and you will be my
               witnesses  in  Jerusalem,  throughout  Judea  and
               Samaria, and to the ends of the earth.” When he had said this, as they were looking on, he was
               lifted up, and a cloud took him from their sight. While they were looking intently at the sky as]]></page><page Index="16"><![CDATA[he  was  going,  suddenly  two  men  dressed  in  white  garments  stood  beside  them.  They  said,
               “Men of Galilee, why are you standing there looking at the sky? This Jesus who has been taken

               up  from  you  into  heaven  will  return  in  the  same  way  as  you  have  seen  him  going  into
               heaven.” Then  they  returned  to  Jerusalem  from  the  mount  called  Olivet,  which  is  near
               Jerusalem, a sabbath day’s journey away. (Acts 1:6-12)

               Heavenly Father,
               Jesus has promised to remain with His Church until the end of time.
               May those who are called to continue His work
                       through the sacraments and holy witness
               be strengthened to carry out your will for the Church.
               We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.

               Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…

               The Descent of the Holy Spirit

                                                               When the time for Pentecost was fulfilled,
                                                               they  were  all  in  one  place  together.  And
                                                               suddenly there came from the sky a noise
                                                               like a strong driving wind, and it filled the
                                                               entire  house  in  which  they  were.  Then
                                                               there  appeared  to  them  tongues  as  of
                                                               fire, which  parted  and  came  to  rest  on
                                                               each one of them. And they were all filled
                                                               with the holy Spirit and began to speak in
                                                               different  tongues, as  the  Spirit  enabled
                                                               them to proclaim. Now there were devout
               Jews from every nation under heaven staying in Jerusalem. At this sound, they gathered in
               a large crowd, but they were confused because each one heard them speaking in his own
               language. They were astounded, and in amazement they asked, “Are not all these people
               who are speaking Galileans?... yet we hear them speaking in our own tongues of the mighty
               acts of God.” (Acts 2:1-7,11)

               Heavenly Father,
               continue to send forth your Spirit
               to renew in your Church
                       the call to serve you in the priesthood and consecrated life.
               May that Holy Spirit always be active in our lives.
               We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.]]></page><page Index="17"><![CDATA[Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…

               The Assumption of the Blessed Virgin Mary


               A great sign appeared in the sky, a woman clothed with the
               sun, with the moon under her feet, and on her head a crown
               of twelve stars. She was with child and wailed aloud in pain
               as she labored to give birth. Then another sign appeared in
               the sky; it was a huge red dragon, with seven heads and ten
               horns, and on its heads were seven diadems. Its tail swept
               away a third of the stars in the sky and hurled them down to
               the earth. Then the dragon stood before the woman about

               to give birth, to devour her child when she gave birth. She
               gave  birth  to  a  son,  a  male  child,  destined  to  rule  all  the
               nations with an iron rod. Her child was caught up to God and
               his  throne.  The  woman  herself  fled  into  the  desert  where
               she had a place prepared by God, that there she might be
               taken care of for twelve hundred and sixty days. (Revelation
               12:1-6)


               Heavenly Father,
               Mary now enjoys the fullness of your life in heaven.
               Help us to realize that you have a plan for each of our lives
               and that our happiness lies in discovering and following that plan.
               We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.

               Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…

                                             The Coronation of Mary, Queen of Heaven and Earth


                                               And Mary said:
                                               “My soul proclaims the greatness of the Lord;
                                               my spirit rejoices in God my savior.
                                               For he has looked upon his handmaid’s lowliness;
                                               behold, from now on will all ages call me blessed.
                                               The Mighty One has done great things for me,
                                               and holy is his name.
                                               His mercy is from age to age
                                               to those who fear him.
                                               He has shown might with his arm,
                                               dispersed the arrogant of mind and heart.
                                               He has thrown down the rulers from their thrones]]></page><page Index="18"><![CDATA[but lifted up the lowly.
                The hungry he has filled with good things;
                the rich he has sent away empty.
                He has helped Israel his servant,
                remembering his mercy,
                according to his promise to our fathers,
                to Abraham and to his descendants forever.” (Luke 1:46-55)


               Heavenly Father,
               it is in humility that we discover how truly great our vocations are.
               Help us to serve you in humble ways
               so that others may see your light, rather than our own.
               We ask this, with Mary, through Christ our Lord.

               Our Father, Hail Mary (10x), Glory be, O My Jesus…]]></page></pages></Search>